You by yourself?
That’s pretty impressive.
Where do you want to die?
I’ll let you decide the location.
I would prefer somewhere remote,
so we won’t be a nuisance.
I wouldn’t want your screams
to bother anyone.
[growls]
[theme song playing]
CONDITION x AND x CONDITION
[narrator] Uvogin seeks to unleash
his rage upon Kurapika.
who seeks his own revenge
against the Phantom Troupe
for his lost brethren.
Both are eager for the battle
which is about to begin.
[Uvogin] [chuckles] There we go!
Are these all leech eggs?
Ew, gross!
Sorry for the holdup.
[Uvogin gulping, refreshed exhale]
Got a question for you.
Who the hell are you?
You’re not normal.
I feel extraordinary determination
in your Nen.
[Kurapika] Before I answer your question,
there’s something I need you to tell me.
Do you remember those you’ve killed?
Any of them?
Yeah, some of ‘em.
But mostly just the ones
who made a lasting impression on me.
This is some kind of vendetta?
Who are you trying to avenge?
The Kurta Clan.
[pensive grunt] I never heard of ‘em.
The Lukso province.
A small clan with scarlet-colored eyes.
And five years ago, you attacked us.
[Uvogin] Scarlet Eyes?
What's that?
Name of a jewel or somethin’?
Yeah, sorry, that doesn’t ring a bell.
But I was definitely a member
five years ago;
I know that much.
[Kurapika] When you kill people…
people who have done no wrong in any way…
how do you feel?
What goes through your mind?
Nothing, really. Not a thing.
[Kurapika] You’re scum.
For your sins...
you’ll pay with your life.
Coming across people like you
is the reason killing never gets old!
You wanna know what gives me
the most pleasure, though?
When someone like you comes for revenge
and I turn the tables on ‘em!
Those chains are trouble.
I’ve got no idea what kind of trickery
he used on ‘em
but those things are infused
with an unreal amount of Nen.
Which means...
That I’ve gotta land the first blow!
That got him.
Whaddya know?
Even after taking that punch,
he’s still had the energy to attack?
Least I busted his left arm.
Huh?
Not a scratch? How?
By how much Nen’s in those chains,
I’d say he’s a Manipulator
who controls things,
or a Conjurer who can materialize aura.
If I had to guess,
I’d say it’s the former.
But only an Enhancer
should be able to block my attack.
What is he?
-[Kurapika] That punch…
-[Uvogin] Huh?
...was it the best you’ve got?
[ticked-off rasp]
[Uvogin chuckles]
[Uvogin] Was that supposed to be funny?
That was only 20 per cent of my strength.
But don’t worry.
This time I’ll be sure to use half!
[roars]
[annoyed grunt]
[groan of pain]
Why, you--!
[roars]
Dammit.
Little punk keeps darting around.
Know what?
Let me guess.
“You’ll regret that you
didn’t use the chain just now.”
-Right?
-[Uvogin] Huh?
[Kurapika] Stop making excuses
and fight me.
You’re wasting my time.
[Uvogin] You want it?
Fine.
[yells] Full throttle!
That’s some intense aura he has.
A smoke screen?
His presence vanished…
He’s using In!
[gasps]
[bones cracking]
I shattered your arm this time.
When I use my Big Bang Impact
at full power,
no exposed flesh in the world can stop it!
But I’m still impressed.
You were quick to react,
I’ll give you that.
I’m guessing you noticed
the slight changes in the smoke and dust.
I am impressed as well.
I didn’t think you knew how to use In.
Striking the ground
to raise a smoke screen
was intended to conceal
not only your physical body
but your entire presence.
However...
you’re not the only one who can use In.
Huh?
N-- No way!
[Kurapika] See them?
So, you can use Gyo, too.
As you may have guessed,
these chains have been conjured
out of Nen.
Meaning I can use In
to render them invisible.
So that’s why you kept them
out in the open all the time?
To trick us all into thinking
they were real?
That’s exactly right.
I pretended I was a Manipulator
utilizing Nen-controlled chains,
so my enemies would focus
on what they saw.
And you just proved that it was effective.
You see, while you took your time
making empty threats,
my chains were already
wrapped around your body.
Capture phase is complete.
[Uvogin growls]
Dammit. But how?
He has an Enhancer’s defenses,
and the Nen in his conjured chains
is incredibly strong.
Has he actually maximized
both Enhancement
and Conjuration abilities?
But that’s impossible!
Isn’t it?
A Nen user is only capable
of achieving a hundred percent mastery
in the type they were born with!
That’s how it works!
ENHANCER
CONJURER
[Kurapika] Seems you’re
having trouble understanding.
Huh?
Let me explain it as a parting gift.
[Uvogin] Those eyes…
Hey, now I remember!
A bunch of ‘em living out
in the middle of nowhere.
The boss really liked those eyes.
And they were all pretty strong, too!
You’re a survivor?
[pleased chuckling]
I’m fired up now!
How about we see what’s stronger…
your silly grudge or my body, huh?
Filthy bastard…
Is that seriously all you can think about?
You will never break these chains!
[roaring]
[tired panting]
What the--?! What’s wrong?
See, I’m not always a Specialist.
It’s Only when my eyes turn scarlet.
Wait, what?
With my Specialist ability,
I use one hundred per cent
of all types of Nen.
ENHANCER -TRANSMUTER - CONJURER
EMITTER - MANIPULATOR
And the name of my power is:
Emperor Time!
[helpless rasp]
[Mizuken] Chains?
[Kurapika] Yes. When you said
I was a Conjurer,
that was the first thing
that came to mind.
[Mizuken] Interesting.
But why chains?
It’s because there are some people
at large in the world right now
who need to be chained to hell.
Oh, is that so?
Because I can’t shake
the nagging suspicion
that you’re the one
who’ll be chained down.
[Kurapika] What the hell do you know?
Wait a sec! Where are you going?
I’m your teacher! Do as I say!
I’m not done talking to you!
Hold on, dammit!
Like I told you,
ordinary chains are pointless!
They’re inferior!
Not only that conjuring
an unbreakable chain...
is impossible!
Really?
Ah, man…
You really are stubborn, aren’t you?
Conjuring unbreakable chains
is impossible.
That being said,
you can conjure something
that’s very close.
Is that so?
[Mizuken] Wow… you only hear
what you want, huh?
[Kurapika] Tell me how!
Make a contract with conditions.
A contract... with conditions?
[Mizuken] Yes. Decide on a condition,
‘a rule, in other words ‘
and swear to abide by it at any cost.
CONDITION
CONTRACT
A contract.
The stricter the limitation,
the more power your ability
will be able to gain from it.
Nen is an additive property,
in most cases.
If Nen adds to your power,
a Nen Contract
multiplies it exponentially.
(ATTACK + NEN) X CONDITION DIFFICULTY
You’ll need to come up
with a condition for your chains,
one that you’re prepared to keep.
But it can be dangerous.
This technique can be incredibly volatile.
It’s a double-edged sword.
If you break the condition that you set,
you stand to lose your Nen abilities...
entirely.
My only objective
is to find my brethren’s scarlet eyes
and capture the Spiders.
So, I want chains that they,
the Phantom Troupe,
will never be able to break.
They will be my only targets.
You’ll use these chains
solely for that objective?
Seems rather weak to me.
Let me finish.
Using the chains
exclusively on the Phantom Troupe
is nothing more than a prerequisite.
All right.
Then what is your rule?
I stake my life on it!
Hey… Kurapika…
When your eyes turn scarlet like that,
it makes your aura look a lot bigger!
Hold on a minute!
Let’s try the Water Divination again!
[Uvogin] A Specialist?
Most people can only use one type of Nen,
but you use all of them?
[Kurapika] That’s correct.
HOLY CHAIN:
HEALING THUMB
I can recover
using enhanced self-healing...
easily.
I completely shattered his left arm
but he healed it instantly!
[Kurapika] There were a number of reasons
I chose you as my first target.
As you fought the Mafia
and the Shadow Beasts,
the other Spiders stayed
completely out of the battle altogether.
That told me
that you preferred to fight alone.
It also made it clear
that they trusted your abilities.
I also prefer to fight one-on-one.
That made you the ideal opponent.
You’re an Enhancer
and you’re proud
of your absolute physical attacks
and defense strength.
In short,
you met every condition
I required for my first target.
You’re a test.
If my Chain Jail works against you,
then it’s a safe bet that it would work
against the rest of you Spiders.
The Chain Jail strips captured Spiders
of their freedom
and, as you may have realized,
enforces Zetsu.
[gasps and grunts]
[Uvogin] I get it…
so that’s why I couldn’t produce any aura!
[straining]
Zetsu, as I’m sure you’re aware by now,
shuts off aura completely.
Meaning that you would need
to use brute strength alone
to break these chains.
[Uvogin] Dammit!
[Kurapika] If the Troupe member
with the most physical strength
can’t break them,
it stands to reason the others
won’t be able to escape them, either.
His enforced Zetsu is bad…
Really bad!
Nen draws its energy from aura…
and if it’s shut off,
you can’t use your power.
A technique for sealing Nen abilities…
This guy’s thought of everything!
[grunt of pain]
Well, that’s good to know.
It would appear that my enhanced fist,
is slightly stronger
than your normal flesh.
That’s valuable information.
[derisive snort]
Provided I’ve chained them,
I can defeat every Troupe member
barehanded.
Now tell me everything you know.
Do not leave anything out.
[pensive exhale]
Where can we find the others?
Kill me.
[grunts in pain]
What abilities do they each have?
[moans in pain] Just kill me.
[Uvogin grunting]
[rasping]
All of this makes me sick.
The way my hand feels...
the grating sound of each strike…
the smell of blood!
Every sensation makes me sick
[seething]
How can you commit such atrocities
and not feel anything?
How is it possible?
Answer me!
Kill me.
[grunt of pain]
This is your final chance.
I have pierced your heart
with the Stake of Retribution.
I am now going to set a rule.
Breaking it will activate the chain
and crush your heart.
JUDGMENT CHAIN:
ARBITER LITTLE FINGER
And the rule is...
that you have to answer
all of my questions truthfully.
Abide by that rule
and I will let you live a bit longer.
Tell me where I can find the others!
[chuckling]
Go to hell, you son of a bitch.
[Uvogin groans]
[thud]
[emotional grunt]
That probably took me longer
than it should have.
[dialing a number]
It's me.
[Melody] Kurapika! What’s going on?
Why didn't you call?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
[Melody] Oh, good…
How are things there?
[Melody] The boss is safe.
She’s asleep in her room.
Unfortunately, due to the weather,
her father won’t be arriving
until late tonight.
[Kurapika] Understood.
Thanks.
[Chrollo] A chain user...
Probably a Manipulator or a Conjurer.
Uvogin can hold his own in a fight…
but one-on-one, he’s most vulnerable
to those two categories.
It’s not uncommon for a Conjurer
to enhance the things he creates.
Many do.
And some of those abilities
could easily render Uvo helpless.
And a Manipulator
could manipulate Uvo himself.
I knew it! I just knew
I should have gone with him! Damn it!
If he fails to return here by dawn…
then we’ll switch plans.
[narrator] Shalnark senses danger
as Uvogin fails to return.
And their leader, Chrollo
begins formulating a plan
to terminate the chain user.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Uvogin!
He’s really big and a member
of the Phantom Troupe!
His ultimate attack
is a Nen-infused straight right punch.
[both] So watch out
for the Big Bang Impact!
[Gon] Next time: “Very x Sharp x Eye”.
It’s so sharp,
it’s like a razor blade or something!
[Killua] Whoa! That sounds awesome!